http://www.brokersinsurancegroup.com/insurance-agency-terms-of-use.htm

Terms of Use
Welcome to the BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP website. We respect the privacy concerns of the users of the Internet and this Web site.
We believe it is important we inform you how we treat the information we receive on the Internet, and provide this privacy
statement to explain what information we collect and how this information may be used.
You can visit the BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP site without revealing personal information about yourself.
We and or our vendors may collect domain names plus the e-mail addresses of only those visitors that choose to provide it.
This information is utilized to measure such items as but not limited to number of visits, pages viewed, etc. BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP
may use this information to measure the use of our site and to make adjustments as needed for improved content.
This site does and may, include various forms that may request that you give us contact information such as but not limited
to your name, mailing and/or e-mail address)demographic information, such as but not limited to your age and gender and profile
data, such as but not limited to your type of business. Personal information will not be sold to third parties. We may use your
contact information to send you items such as newsletters or information about us. You can inform us if you would like to
discontinue receiving future mailings.
The BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP Web site may also contain links to other Web sites. We try to provide only links to sites that support our
dedication to high standards and respect for your privacy.
However, we cannot be responsible for the content or the privacy
practices of these other sites.
Furthermore, BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP has no control over these external internet addesses and therefore
cannot gurantee any information or any part of these external sites.
Please review any terms and conditions set forth by those
individual sites.
Security for all personal information is important to us. However, no data transmission via the Internet can be guaranteed to
be 100% secure. While we strive to protect your personal information, The BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP Web site cannot ensure or warrant the
security of any information you transmit to us through this Web site, and you do so at your own risk. Once your transmission
is received, we will do our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.
BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP may make changes to this Privacy Notice by posting it on this site and at the sole discrestion of the
BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP.
Please review our notice for changes on a regular basis.
Terms of Use
This Web site is provided by BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP. By visiting this site, you agree to abide by the terms and conditions set forth in
this notice or included as part of our privacy statement. If you do not agree to abide by these terms and conditions, simply do
not use the site.
The BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP grants you access to materials contained herein. You agree not to interrupt or attempt to interrupt the
operation of this Web site in any way.
BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP authorizes you to only view the information on our Web site. BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP does not authorize you, and you are
strictly forbidden, to copy information from this site to use, publicly display, or distribute or otherwise use for any
commercial purpose without the expressed written permission of BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP.
The BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP Web site may contain links to other Web sites. By visiting those sites, you agree to abide by any terms and
conditions set forth in the notices of those sites.
Disclaimer: MATERIAL CONTAINED IN THIS WEB SITE MAY CONTAIN INFORMATIONAL OR FACTUAL INACCURACIES AND OR
TYPOGRAPHICAL
ERRORS. BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR ANY CONTENT AND INFORMATION PROVIDED WITHIN, OR ANY
CIRCUMSTANCES ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OTHER WEB SITES THAT ARE LINKED TO OR FROM THIS WEB SITE. ANY AND ALL RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THOSE SITES IS SOLELY WITH THAT RESPECTIVE SITE OWNERS.
YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT ANY RELIANCE ON ANY OPINION, ADVICE, STATEMENT AND OR INFORMATION SHALL BE AT YOUR OWN RISK.
BROKERS INSURANCE GROUP RESERVES THE RIGHT, AT ITS SOLE DISCRETION, TO CORRECT ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN ANY PART OF THIS WEB SITE.
Get a Quick Quote
Corporate 1719 Banks RoadMargate FL 33063Phone: (954) 781-0087Toll-free: (877) 325-9218Fax: (954) 773-2908Email  Directions
Testimonials
“Ron is really the best. He knows his industry inside and out. He has such a great personality that he almost makes insurance fun! The best thing about working with Ron is that he is so honest. If you can get a better product or price elsewhere, he'll tell you. I can easily recommend Ron to everyone.” Delray Beach, Florida
Gary Press
More...
